export const questions = [
    {
      questionText: "When was Avengers-End Game released?",
      answerOptions: [
        { answerText: "2021", isCorrect: false },
        { answerText: "2018", isCorrect: false },
        { answerText: "2020", isCorrect: false },
        { answerText: "2019", isCorrect: true },
      ],
    },
    {
      questionText:
        "What are the dying words of Charles Foster Kane in Citizen Kane?",
      answerOptions: [
        { answerText: "“Rose lad”", isCorrect: false },
        { answerText: "“Rosebud”", isCorrect: true },
      ],
    },
    {
      questionText: "What’s the name of the skyscraper in Die Hard?",
      answerOptions: [
        { answerText: "Nakatomi Plaza", isCorrect: true },
        { answerText: "Nakatomo Plaza", isCorrect: false },
      ],
    },
    {
      questionText: "In The Matrix, does Neo take the red pill?",
      answerOptions: [
        { answerText: "True", isCorrect: true },
        { answerText: "False", isCorrect: false },
      ],
    },
    {
      questionText:
        "What pop vocal group performs at the wedding in Bridesmaids?",
      answerOptions: [
        { answerText: "Phillip", isCorrect: false },
        { answerText: "Wilson Phillips", isCorrect: true },
        { answerText: "The Phillips", isCorrect: false },
      ],
    },
    {
      questionText: "What is the highest-grossing R-rated movie of all time?",
      answerOptions: [
        { answerText: "Joker", isCorrect: true },
        { answerText: "Django", isCorrect: false },
      ],
    },
    {
      questionText:
        'In "The Lion King," Mufasa dies from being trampled by a pack of:?',
      answerOptions: [
        { answerText: "Wildebeasts", isCorrect: true },
        { answerText: "Buffalos", isCorrect: false },
      ],
    },
    {
      questionText:
        'Finish this line from "Jaws": "You re gonna need a bigger ________."',
      answerOptions: [
        { answerText: "Boat", isCorrect: true },
        { answerText: "Gun", isCorrect: false },
      ],
    },
    {
      questionText:
        "What 1970 movie marked the feature debut of Arnold Schwarzenegger?",
      answerOptions: [
        { answerText: "Hercules in New York ", isCorrect: true },
        { answerText: "Hercules 1970", isCorrect: false },
      ],
    },
    {
      questionText: "Who wrote the screenplay for Rocky?",
      answerOptions: [
        { answerText: "Steven Seagull", isCorrect: false },
        { answerText: "John Wick", isCorrect: false },
        { answerText: "Sylvester Stallone", isCorrect: true },
        { answerText: "Rambo", isCorrect: false },
      ],
    },
  ];
